Zaki Nusseibeh Collection AD.MC.020
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Sheikh Zayed, Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum and Zaki Nusseibeh with British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher., 1981; ref74; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed with Indira Gandhi and Zaki Nusseibeh., February 1975; ref75; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Color Photography; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Furnishings; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh covered in flower petals during a trip to India., February 1975; ref76; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; India; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Microphones; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed seated next to Zulfikar Ali Bhutto with Zaki Nusseibeh taking notes., Circa 1970; ref77; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Men; Political Leadership; Pens/Inkwells; Furnishings; Audio cassette
- Sheikh Zayed walking with President Fakhruddin Ali Ahmed and Zaki Nusseibeh in the middle., 1975; ref78; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Cameras
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh walking in front of the Great Gate of Taj Mahal., February 1975; ref79; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Political Leadership; Photographic Prints; Agra, India; Color Photography; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Uniforms; Architecture; Buildings; Military/Soldiers; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Islamic Architecture; Monuments
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibah with a crowd gathered around a red motorcycle during India visit., February 1975; ref80; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Men; Crowds; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Motorcycles; Color Photography; Military/Soldiers; Transportation; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh walking in front of the Hauz Khas Pavillions., February 1975; ref81; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Monuments; Islamic Architecture; Color Photography; Architecture; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Delhi, India; Monuments; Outdoors; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh covered in yellow flower petals during a visit to India., February 1975; ref82; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Color Photography; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Microphones; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh covered in yellow flower petals during a visit to India., February 1975; ref83; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Color Photography; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed talking to reporters next to Zaki Nusseibeh during his visit to the Aligarh Muslim University., February 1975; ref84; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Political Leadership; Aligarh, Uttar Pradesh, India; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Microphones; Color Photography; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Outdoors; Universities
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Zaki Nusseibeh and a group of men in front of The Iron Pillar of Delhi., February 1975; ref85; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Monuments; Color Photography; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Delhi, India; Outdoors; Monuments; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with a man., Circa 1970; ref86; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Hats; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed wearing flower garlands, walking next to men., Circa 1970; ref87; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed standing on a stage during a visit to India with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., February 1975; ref88; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; India; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Military/Soldiers; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Turban; Tents; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh gathered around an architectural model display of a mosque., Circa 1970; ref89; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Architecture; Islamic Architecture; Mosques; Military/Soldiers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed next to Zulfikar Ali Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1974; ref90; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Men; Medals; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Medals
- Group portrait of Sheikh Zayed, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1974; ref91; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Group Portraits; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed holding a child, with a crowd gathered around them., Circa 1970; ref92; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; India; Sheikhs; Men; Crowds; Children; Girls; Military/Soldiers; Insignia/Emblem; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh with Benazir Bhutto are greeted with flowers., Circa 1990; ref93; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Women; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Children; Girls; Boys; Military/Soldiers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Head Covers/Veils; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed with Benazir Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh in front of a UAE airplane., Circa 1990; ref94; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Women; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Airplanes; Crowds; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Head Covers/Veils; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed with Benazir Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh in front of a UAE airplane., Circa 1990; ref95; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Women; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Airplanes; Crowds; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh with a group of men at the opening of the reception hall at the Pakistan Institute of Nuclear Science and Technology., 9 May 1972; ref96; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Islamabad, Pakistan; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Military/Soldiers; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed talking to reporters at a desk with Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., Circa 1970; ref97; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikhs; Men; Women; Microphones; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Furnishings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed standing beside a commemorative plaque for Sheikh Zayed Women's Hospital Larkana next to Zaki Nusseibeh., 12 March 1974; ref98; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Hospitals; English Writing; Women; Larkana, Pakistan; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed wearing a dagger with Khalifa bin Hamad Al Thani., 1969; ref99; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Police; Cars; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Swords/Knives; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Uniforms; Weapons; Transportation; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Portrait of Sheikh Zayed., Circa 1970; ref100; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Swords/Knives; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Weapons; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan and men., Circa 1970; ref101; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Flags; Buildings; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- A collage of Sheikh Zayed with Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan., Circa 1970; ref102; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Birds; Children; Boys; Individual Portraits; Animals; Political Leadership
- A portrait of Sheikh Zayed with Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan., Circa 1970; ref103; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Children; Boys; Sheikhs; Group Portraits; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Clocks/Watches; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed holding a falcon., Circa 1970; ref104; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Birds; Animals; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Arabic Calligraphy; Drinks/Beverages; Art; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed and Abd Al Jalil Mohammed Al Fahim with a falcon and a group of men., Circa 1970; ref105; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Animals; Birds; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Drinks/Beverages; Electricity; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed with Sheikh Maktoum Al Maktoum and Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan and men., Circa 1970; ref106; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Men; Political Leadership; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb
- Sheikh Zayed holding a falcon sitting next to a man., Circa 1970; ref107; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Animals; Birds; Arabic Calligraphy; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Books; Art; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed with soldiers at a memorial with Zaki Nusseibeh in the back., Circa 1990; ref108; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Military/Soldiers; Memorials; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Insignia/Emblem; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Uniforms
- Sheikh Zayed at an event., Circa 1970; ref109; Joseph (UAE); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Audiences/Spectators; Events/Occasions; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Cameras; Uniforms; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Sheikh Zayed with Chad President Francois Tombalbaye, with Zaki Nusseibeh standing., Circa 1970; ref110; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Cigarettes; Furnishings; Political Leadership; Interiors
- Zaki Nusseibeh in a crowd of leaders and dignitaries., Circa 1970; ref111; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals; Insignia/Emblem; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with a man with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., Circa 1970; ref112; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed sitting next to a man in front of Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref113; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE); 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Furnishings; Political Leadership; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Senegal President Léopold Sédar Senghor and Zaki Nusseibeh., 7 November 1975; ref114; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Canes/Walking Sticks; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Arabic Writing; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed walking with President of Zaire Mobutu Sese Seko and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref115; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Canes/Walking Sticks; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Hats; Furnishings; Chandeliers; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed seated next to Somali President Siad Barre., Circa 1970; ref116; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb
- Sheikh Zayed with Somali President Siad Barre, Zaki Nusseibeh and Ahmed Bin Hamid Al Qubaisi., Circa 1970; ref117; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Cigarettes
- Sheikh Zayed sitting at a coffee table with Somali President Siad Barre, Ahmed Bin Hamid Al Qubaisi and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref118; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Furnishings; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Food; Drinks/Beverages
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Chad President Francois Tombalbaye., Circa 1970; ref119; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed with Archbishop President Makarios of Cyprus and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1975; ref120; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Religious Clothing; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Priests/Clergymen; Interiors; Furnishings; Orthodox Christianity; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Archbishop President Makarios of Cyprus., 1975; ref121; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Religious Clothing; Priests/Clergymen; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Outdoors; Orthodox Christianity
- Indira Gandhi at a press conference with Zaki Nusseibah., Circa 1970; ref122; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; India; Political Leadership; Men; Women; Microphones; Traditional Dress; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Radios; Furnishings; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh walking with a group in front of the Southern Gate of Taj Mahal., Circa 1970; ref123; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Agra, India; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Microphones; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Monuments
- A group portrait of the UAE and USA delegations with Sheikh Khalifa, Sheikh Mohammad, Zaki Nusseibeh and President Bill Clinton in the Oval Office at the Whitehouse., Circa 2000; ref124; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Washington (D.C.); United States of America; Political Leadership; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Color Photography; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Furnishings; Offices; Men; Paintings; Art; Interiors
- An overhead view of Sheikh Zayed with French President Valéry Giscard d'Estaing at a gathering of officials., 1975; ref125; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tapestry; Audiences/Spectators; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Paris, France; Political Leadership; Men; Microphones; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Art; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed walking with French President Valéry Giscard d'Estaing and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1975; ref126; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Paris, France; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh walking with Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran in front of Azadi Tower., Circa 1970; ref127; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Cameras; Political Leadership; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Monuments; Tehran, Iran; Outdoors; Hats
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh walking with Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran in front of Azadi Tower., Circa 1970; ref128; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Monuments; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Canes/Walking Sticks; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Tehran, Iran; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed with Yasser Arafat, Bruno Kreisky and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref129; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Furnishings; Art; Paintings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Telephones; Political Leadership; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed with Yasser Arafat, Bruno Kreisky and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref130; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Furnishings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Art; Paintings; Telephones; Political Leadership; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed and a group of people at the Great Wall of China., May 1990; ref131; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Flags; Color Photography; China; Men; Women; Crowds; Monuments; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Outdoors; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed with Emperor Akihito of Japan and Zaki Nusseibeh., May 1990; ref132; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Tokyo, Japan; Color Photography; Men; Paintings; Furnishings; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Art; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Bow Ties; Handkerchiefs; Interiors
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Nelson Mandela on a state visit with Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1995; ref133; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Color Photography; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Flags; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors
- A group portrait of the rulers of the United Arab Emirates. Sheikh Mohammed, Sheikh Khalifa, Sheikh Sultan, Sheikh Hamdan, Sheikh Mansour, Sheikh Abdullah, Sheikh Saif, Sheikh Ahmed, Sheikh Saeed, Sheikh Falah, Sheikh Nasser, Sheikh Nahyan, Sheikh Issa, Sheikh Hazza, Sheikh Tahnoon., Circa 1970; ref134; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Family; Canes/Walking Sticks; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Nelson Mandela on a red carpet with Zaki Nusseibeh., 1995; ref135; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Outdoors; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Sheikh Zayed and Nelson Mandela receiving gifts from Emirati girls with Zaki Nusseibeh., 1995; ref136; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)